Locke先生?
Mr. Locke?
Locke先生 你能听见我说话么?
Mr. Locke, can you hear me?
你醒了 恭喜啊
Welcome back.
我认识你
I know you.
我们搭乘过同一班从悉尼来的飞机
We were on the same flight back from Sydney.
曾在行李认领申报处见过面
I met you in the baggage claim office.
你的刀掉了
You had lost your knives.
我是Jack Shephard
I'm Jack Shephard.
我怎么了?
What happened?
你被车撞了 刚做完手术
You were run down by a car. You just came out of surgery.
我...
Am I...
我没事吧?
Am I all right?
你的硬脊膜囊破裂
Your dural sac ruptured.
不过 手术很成功 一切都会复原的
But I think I got everything back where it belongs.
Locke先生 在动手术的时候 我看了一下
Mr. Locke, while I was operating, I got a look
你脊椎之前受的伤...
at the initial injury to your spine...
就是累及你坐轮椅的伤处
The one that put you in the wheelchair.
我希望你能告诉我 受伤的原因
And I was hoping you could tell me how that happened.
凭什么?
Why?
因为我觉得你符合候选人的条件
Because I think you're a candidate.
哪种候选人?
A candidate for what?
我们正在研发的
A new procedure,
一种新型外科手术 还有...
a surgery we're developing, and...
如果它生效的话 你的腿就能恢复知觉了
if it works, it could restore feeling to your legs.
说不准 你还可以重新站起来走路
In fact, you may even walk again.
如果你让我试试 Locke先生
If you'll give me a shot, Mr. Locke,
我觉得... 我可以治好你
I think that... that I could fix you.
不 谢谢
No, thank you.
手术几乎没什么风险 而且... 如果你康复了...
Well, now there's minimal risk, and... and the benefit could...
医生 我说了不用
I said no, doctor.
John啊?
John?
哦
Oh.
哦 John
Oh, John.
- 他们总算让我见你了 - 哦!
- It's the first time they let me see you. - Oh!
你... 你还好么?
Are... are you okay?
我没事 别担心
I'm fine. Hi.
你是他的主治医生么?
Are you his doctor?
嗯 没错 我是Shephard医生
Yes, I am. Dr. Shephard.
哦 谢谢你
Oh, thank you.
谢谢 谢谢你救了他
Thank you. Thank you for saving him.
谢谢
Thank you.
欢迎来到九头蛇岛
Welcome to Hydra Island.
至少 你不用划桨 就已经到了
At least you didn't have to paddle.
进来吧
Get in.
啊哈
Unh-unh.
我才不要进这些笼子里去
Ain't no way I'm gettin' back in those cages.
- 我手上可拿着枪呢 你... - 现在没了 兵哥哥
- Well, I've got the gun, so you... - Not anymore, doughboy.
把枪放下!
Drop the gun!
放下枪 否则我杀了她
Put the gun down or I'll kill her!
你不会杀人的
You ain't gonna kill anybody.
否则 你就不会把我们关到笼子里去了
Otherwise, you wouldn't be throwing us in a cage.
我这儿有份名单 Ford 上面有你的大名
I have a list of names. Ford, you're on it,
还有Reyes和Kwon夫妇
As are Reyes and the Kwons.
- 名单上有Kate Austen吗? - 没有她
- Kate Austen? - She's not.
所以她是死是活 我才不在乎
It doesn't matter to me whether she lives or dies.
别听他的
Don't listen to him.
你或许不信
You may not believe it,
但我是为了你好
but I'm doing this for your own good.
你说得没错 我不相信
You're right. I don't believe it.
- 守卫来了吗? - 他们说大概还要一个小时
- Is the fence live yet? - They're saying about an hour.
我们没那么多时间 叫他们快一点儿
We haven't got an hour. Tell them to work faster.
他就快来了
He's coming.
迷失 第6季第14集
你好?
Hello?
打扰一下?
Excuse me?
- 你好? - 嗯?
- Hello? - Hmm?
哦!
Oh!
抱歉 前台没人
I'm sorry. There was no one out front,
我听见这里有钻机的声音
and I heard the drill.
- 我想找Nadler医生 您知道他在哪儿么? - 远在天边 近在眼前
- Do you know where I can find Dr. Nadler? - Well, you can find him right here.
如果你不是病人 你可以直接叫我Bernard
And if you're not a patient, you can call me Bernard.
嗨
Hi.
我叫Jack Shephard
Jack Shephard.
呃 我是St. Sebastian医院的外科医生
Um, I'm a surgeon over at St. Sebastian,
我想借您手下一名患者的资料看看
and I was hoping to get a look at one of your patient files.
这位病患的名字是?
And which patient would that be?
他叫John Locke 我们有资料显示
His name's John Locke, and our records said
你曾给他做过一个急诊手术
that you had done some emergency oral surgery on him
这大概是三年前的事了
about three years back.
- 那你到底想探寻些什么? - 我想知道他受伤的原因
- And what are you looking for, exactly? - I wanna know how he was hurt.
你介意我问问
Do you mind if I ask you
你为何对Locke先生如此感兴趣么 Jack?
why you're so interested in Mr. Locke, Jack?
呃...
Um...
大约一周前 我遇见了他
He and I met about a week ago.
- 我们乘坐的 是来自澳大利亚的同一班飞机 - 大洋航班815
- We were on the same flight back from Australia. - Oceanic 815.
我的座位 跟你之间隔了条走道
I sat across the aisle from you.
如果你还记得的话
If memory serves,
你当时还跟我妻子Rose调情来着
you were flirting with my wife Rose
而我去了卫生间
when I was in the bathroom.
无巧不成书 对吧?
It's pretty weird, huh?
嗯
Yeah.
呃... 或许有些事 你心知肚明 对吧?
Well... Maybe you're on to something here, hmm?
病人的资料是保密的
Now I can't break patient confidentiality
我不能违反规定 私自透露
and tell you something I shouldn't,
但我可以告诉你 当我给Locke先生治疗的时候
But I can tell you that when I treated Mr. Locke,
和他一同出事的 还有另一个男人
there was another man in the same accident with him.
等等 这是... 三年前的事了
Wait, that was... three years ago.
你还... 记得?
You just... remember that?
当然了 Jack
Of course I do, Jack.
是Anthony Cooper
Anthony Cooper.
祝你好运 医生
Good luck, doc.
我希望你能得偿所愿
I hope you find what you're looking for.
发生什么事了?
What happened?
我们遭到了迫击炮轰
There was a mortar attack.
Widmore的人朝我们开火
Widmore's people fired on us.
Locke救了你
Locke saved you.
其他人呢?
What about the rest of your group?
他们怎么了?
What happened to them?
没死的人 都逃进了丛林
The ones who weren't killed scattered into the jungle.
现在只剩3个人了
It's just the three of us now.
他干嘛带我来这儿?
Why did he bring me here?
因为你的朋友被抓了
Because your friends got themselves captured.
现在...
And now...
我们要去救他们
we're gonna have to rescue them.
到哪里去救?
Rescue them from what?
Widmore把他们关在一个笼子里 大约在半英里开外的内陆
Widmore has them in a cage about a half a mile inland.
他干嘛...
Why would he...
我会问他的
You know, I would ask him,
只是 我觉得他不会直截了当地告诉我
except I don't think he's gonna give me a straight answer.
而且 我觉得他居心叵测
But I can't imagine that his intentions are good.
如果我们现在动身
If we move right now,
我们可以杀Widmore一个措手不及
we can break your people out, run for the plane
救出你的人 然后冲上飞机 离开这个岛
and be off this island before Widmore knows what hit him.
他们不是我的人
They're not my people.
我也不会离开这个岛
And I'm not leaving the island.
好吧 Jack
Well, Jack,
我希望你有朝一日 能改变主意
I'm hoping you'll still change your mind about that.
不过你的朋友们 可是想死了要走
But your friends do want to leave.
由于之前他们撇开我 驾着我的船跑了
And since they just ran away from me on my own boat,
我需要你帮我劝服他们
I'm gonna need your help convincing them
让他们相信我
that they can trust me.
我凭什么相信你?
Why should I trust you?
因为此时此刻 我可以杀了你
Because I could kill you, Jack, right here, right now.
我还可以杀掉你的每一个朋友
And I could kill every single one of your friends,
而你却无力阻拦
and there's not a thing that you could do to stop me.
可我没有杀你 相反 我救了你
But instead of killing you, I saved your life.
而且我也想救他们
And now I wanna save them, too.
所以 你会帮我吗?
So will you help me?
我们真像是在兜圈子 对吧?
You feel like we're runnin' in circles?
兜来兜去还在笼子里...
Back in these cages...
除了上次 被人拿枪指着脑袋
Except last time, the gun was to my head.
他不会杀我的 James
He wouldn't have killed me, James.
我上次告诉你的那个洞穴
That cave I told you about,
就是写满了人名的那个 还记得么?
where all the names are written?
那里也刻着你的名字
Your name was there, too,
但被划掉了
But it was crossed out.
他不需要你了 Kate
He doesn't need you, Kate.
那么 是你妈在带她?
So she's with your mother?
嗯 你看过她的照片了? 怎么看见的?
Yes. You saw her pictures? How?
Widmore的人 在飞机上找到了你的照相机
Widmore's people found your camera on the plane.
他给我看了里面的相片
He showed me the pictures.
我们的女儿...
Our daughter...
她真漂亮
She's so beautiful.
你的戒指在我这儿呢
I have your ring.
啊哦
Uh-oh.
怎么了?
What happened?
谁把电关了? 到底怎么了?
Somebody shut us down? What's going on?
- 有人把电源切断了 - 快派一队人去发电机那儿!
- Somebody killed the power. - Get a team to that generator now!
我们死定了
And we're dead.
上! 上! 上!
Go! Go! Go!
啊!
Aah!
嘿
Hey.
我想我应该能够得着钥匙
I think I can reach the keys.
- 快点儿 等那东西解决了他们 就轮到我们了 - 我可受不了坐以待毙
- Hurry. When that thing's done with them, he's coming for us. - Well, I ain't waitin'.
啊!
Uhh!
该死的!
Damn it!
你来这儿干嘛?
What are you doing here?
我和他一起来的 快走
I'm with him. Come on.
离飞机还有多远?
How much further to the plane?
大概还有四分之一英里 翻过山就到了
I'd say about a quarter-mile, just over that ridge.
那么 你打算和我们一起走了?
So you're coming with us now?
我会送你们去飞机那儿 但我不登机
I'm gonna take you to the plane, but I'm not getting on it.
抱歉 Kate 我...
I'm sorry, Kate. I'm...
我不想走
I'm not meant to go.
谢谢你回来救我们 感激涕零
Thanks for coming back for us, doc. Appreciate it.
别开枪
No, it's okay.
Sayid不是坏人 发电机就是他关掉的
Sayid's with us. He was the one who turned off the generators.
那敢情好 多多益善
Great. The more the merrier.
我们该走了 Locke在等着呢
We need to go. Locke's waiting.
您是Cooper先生的亲戚么?
Are you a relative of Mr. Cooper's?
呃 不 我不是 但是...
Uh, no. No, I'm not, but...
我... 可以问问您所来何事么?
M... may I ask the nature of the visit?
- 呃... - Shephard医生?
- Um... - Dr. Shephard?
嘿
Hey.
您来这儿有事?
What are you doing here?
呃 我来找Anthony Cooper
Um, I'm here to see Anthony Cooper.
你认识他吗? 你也是来找他的?
Do you know him? Is that why you're here, too?
您找Anthony干嘛?
What do you want with Anthony?
我想找他谈谈
I wanna talk to him
他和Locke先生出的那场事故
about the accident that he was in with Mr. Locke.
呃 Shephard医生...
Um, Dr. Shephard...
您还是走吧
Just go.
听我说 我只是想帮他而已
Look, all I wanna do is help him.
我知道 John跟我说过手术的事
I know. John told me about the operation.
他不想做
He doesn't want it.
为什么他不想做?
Why doesn't he want it?
拜托 Shephard医生 请您别管这事了
Please, Dr. Shephard, just leave this alone.
您救了John的命
You saved John's life.
为何不能就此收手?
Why can't that be enough?
因为还没到收手的时候
Because it's not.
家政服务 请拨23
Housekeeping, dial 23.
家政服务 分机号23
Housekeeping, extension 23.
嗨
Hi.
这就是Anthony Cooper
This is Anthony Cooper.
他是John的父亲
He's John's father.
喂! 停下!
Hey! Stop!
快在那停下!
Stop right there!
好 就是这了
Well, all righty.
我们来看看怎么让这家伙飞起来
Let's see what it'll take to get this baby to fly.
这混蛋
Son of a bitch.
他的脖子断了
His neck's been broken.
那是我弄断的
That's because I broke it.
说些让你们觉得安慰的话
If it's any consolation,
Widmore早知道我会杀了这些人
Widmore knew that I would kill these men.
- 你说什么? - 他们守着这飞机 只不过是装装样子而已
- What are you talking about? - They were only guarding the plane for show.
如果Charles真的打算
If Charles had really wanted
阻止我登机
to keep me from actually getting on board,
他就不会撤掉防御
he wouldn't have moved his little fences.
等等 那他现在是想让我们离开这座岛?
Well, wait. Now he wants us to leave the island?
不是的 Hugo 他是想在同一个地方同一时间
No, Hugo. He wants to get us all in the same place
抓住我们所有人...
at the same time...
这飞机条件绝佳 空间又小 我们根本没希望逃出去
A nice, confined space we have no hope of getting out of.
他可以把我们一网打尽
And then he wants to kill us.
- 用什么杀了我们? - 就用这个
- Kill us with what? - With this.
4块塑胶炸弹
4 bricks of C4.
我在飞机一个行李架上发现它们的
I found 'em in one of the overhead compartments,
它们与飞机的电路系统相连
wired to the electrical system of the plane.
如果我们打开电路...
If we would've turned it on...
轰
Boom.
那现在怎么办?
So what now?
我们无法确定 飞机上是否还有其它炸药
We can't be sure he didn't put more explosives on the plane.
这样登机不安全 如果我们打算离开这岛
It's not safe. If we're gonna leave the island,
我想我们只能乘坐潜艇
I think we have to take the submarine.
- 我就说嘛 - 兄弟 等等
- Well, that's what I've been sayin' all along. - Dude, wait.
他并不打算离开这个岛
He's not supposed to leave the island.
- 我是说 Alpert是这么说的... - 去他的Alpert 他又不在这
- I mean, Alpert said... - Screw Alpert. He ain't here.
你救了我们两次
That's twice you've saved our asses.
我想是我误会你了
Guess I was wrong about you.
谢谢 James
Thank you, James.
那潜艇应该有重兵把守
That submarine is gonna be heavily defended.
只要我们都在 一切不成问题
We're gonna need everyone.
我会帮你 但如我之前所说 我不会和你走的
I'll help you, but like I said, I'm not going with you.
可以
Fair enough.
我们走吧
Let's go.
嗨
Hey.
- 我... 我很抱歉 我... - 没关系 Claire
- I... I'm sorry that I... - That's all right, Claire.
我理解你为什么跟他们一边
I understand why you went with them.
喂 医生 听着
Hey, doc, listen up.
你不想离开这岛
You don't wanna leave this island,
那是你他妈自己的事
that's your own damn business.
但我还想要你帮最后一次忙
But I'm gonna ask you for one last favor.
我一点也不相信那个东西
I don't trust that thing one bit,
所以我需要你帮帮我
so here's what I need you to do.
当我们到了码头
Once we get to the dock,
你要保证那东西上不了潜艇
you make sure it doesn't get on the sub.
我应该怎么做? 你刚刚也看到了它的能耐
How am I supposed to do that? You saw what it did back there.
把它弄到水里去 其它的我来搞定
Just get it in the water. I'll take care of the rest.
Locke先生 你醒了吗?
Mr. Locke, are you awake?
按下按钮
Push the button.
Locke先生 你听到我说话吗?
Mr. Locke, can you hear me?
我希望你能相信我的话
I wish you had believed me.
打扰下?
Excuse me?
Littleston小姐?
Ms. Littleton?
Shephard医生 我... 我正在找你
Dr. Shephard. I... I was just looking for you.
那个 嗯 那个律师告诉我 你在这工作
The, um, the lawyer told me you work here.
嗯 我们... 可以聊聊吗?
Um, c... can we talk?
当然 当然
Yes. Yes.
噢 不用了 没事
Oh. No. I'm okay.
抱歉 前几天
Sorry I had to run out
宣读... 遗嘱的时候 我却离场了
of the... the will reading the other day,
- 因为我得做一个紧急手术 而且... - 噢 别... 别担心
- but I did have an emergency and... - Oh. N... no worries.
嗯 我知道你跟我一样 觉得很别扭
Um, I know this is as awkward for you as it is for me.
我甚至从没见过那个男人
I never even met this man.
不管怎样吧 啊 那个律师把这个给我了
Anyway, the, uh, the lawyer gave me this.
她说 嗯 还有其它的东西要给我
She said, uh, there'd be more stuff to come,
但这是我父亲特意想要我拿着的
but that my father especially wanted me to have this.
你知道为什么
You know why
或者这是什么意思吗?
or what it's supposed to mean?
我不知道
I have no idea.
而且...
But then...
我... 我也不了解你
I... I didn't know about you, either.
我们的父亲 啊...
Our father, uh...
若果你... 不介意 我可以知道他是怎么死的吗?
You mind... you mind if I ask how he died?
在悉尼某酒吧外的小巷里 有人发现他横尸在那儿
He was found in an alley outside a bar in Sydney.
他是因为酗酒致死
He drank himself to death.
我飞到悉尼 把他的遗体运回来
I flew down to bring his body back,
但是后来 嗯... 那趟航班把它遗失了
but then, uh... the airline lost it.
我前几天刚从悉尼飞回来
I just flew in from Sydney few days ago.
什么时候?
When?
嗯 上周三
Uh, last Wednesday.
大洋航空815?
Oceanic flight 815?
啊... 是的
Uh... Yeah.
你介意我看看那个吗?
Do you mind if I have a look at that?
当然不 你看吧
Um, sure. Go ahead.
很抱歉 我... 我也希望我知道为什么他要你拿着这个
I'm sorry. I... I wish I knew why he wanted you to have this.
我...
I...
是啊 我也是
Yeah. Me too.
那么 嗯 很高兴再见到你
Well, um, it was nice seeing you again.
嗯...
Um...
谢谢你尝试帮我
Thanks for trying to help.
你现在住哪?
Where are you staying?
啊 就在街尾的... 汽车旅馆
Uh, just down the road... a motel.
为什么不搬过来和我一起住?
Why don't you come stay with me?
和你一起住?
Stay with you?
我是说 我们... 我们还是陌生人
I mean, we're... we're strangers.
不 我们不是陌生人 我们...
No, we're not strangers. We're...
我们是一家人
We're family.
码头上没有守卫
Just 'cause there ain't any goons on the dock
不能说明潜艇里也没有
doesn't mean they ain't on the sub.
我们有场硬仗要打 知道吗?
We're going in hard. Got it?
Lapidus Hugo Jin Sun... 你们和我一起
Lapidus, Hugo, Jin, Sun... you're with me.
其他人等30秒 然后跟着我们向码头前进
The rest of you wait 30 seconds, head down the dock behind us.
你俩殿后 没问题吧?
You think you two can get our backs?
当然
Absolutely.
好吧
All right.
我们回家吧
Let's go home.
先是发动机房
After engine room,
然后再给底舱动力
power the bilges.
请先给发动机房动力 然后是底舱
After engine room, power the bilges, please.
船长在哪?
Where's the damn captain?
举起手来
Put your damn hands up.
抱歉 无关私怨
Nothin' personal.
嗯 Hoss 你来准备发动这个东西 怎样?
Okay, Hoss, how about you get ready to fire this thing up?
我来
I got it.
我们上
Let's go.
你确定你不再重新考虑下 Jack?
You sure you won't reconsider, Jack?
是 我确定
Yeah, I'm sure.
告诉你 你得留下来的人
Whoever told you you needed to stay
根本不知道他们在说什么
had no idea what they were talking about.
John Locke告诉我 我得留下来
John Locke told me I needed to stay.
怎么了?
What happened?
Kate啊
Kate?!
啊!
Aah!
Claire啊
Claire!
我们快走!
Let's go now!
上面是怎么了?
What's going on up there?
怎么了?
What happened?
Widmore的人打中了她
Widmore's people shot her.
Hurley... Hurley 给我急救药箱
Hurley... Hurley, I need a first aid kit.
- 还有谁在上面? - Claire
- Who else is up there? - Claire.
Claire啊
Claire!
James啊
James!
Lapidus 如果你听到的话...
Lapidus, if you can hear me...
下潜! 下潜!
Dive! Dive!
开动了!
Let's go!
嗨!
Hey!
Claire! Claire 等! 等! 等!
Claire! Claire, wait! Wait! Wait!
Claire! Claire 等下!
Claire! Claire. Wait!
你在搞什么玩意?
What the hell are you doing?
我们来这里就是为这个... 离开这里
What we came here to do... leaving.
- 没事了 没事了 - 不!
- It's all right. It's all right. - No!
他们抛弃我们了!
They're leaving us!
不 相信我 没上潜艇 你不会后悔的
No, trust me. You don't want to be on that sub.
- Claire啊 - Kate
- Claire? - Kate.
- Claire? Claire在哪里? - 她还在上面呢
- Claire? Where's Claire? - She's still up there.
- 不 我们不能丢下她 我们不能... - Kate呀 Kate
- No, we can't leave without her. We can't... - Kate. Kate.
- 她会好起来的吗? - Jack 我找不到急救药箱 兄弟
- Is she gonna be okay? - Jack, I can't find the first aid kit, dude.
Jin... 我的包
Jin... my pack.
那里或许有条衬衫什么的 我可以用它来止血
There might be a shirt in there I can use for pressure.
没事的 放轻松些 一切都会好起来的
It's okay. Just relax. Everything's gonna be all right.
给你 你可以救她吗?
Here. Can you help her?
我想子弹
I think the bullet
- 穿透了... - 穿透什么了?
- went straight through... - What?
哥们 那玩意哪儿来的?
Dude, where'd that come from?
Locke放的
Locke.
我们正中他的下怀
We did exactly what he wanted.
- 我们必须到回到水面上去 - 都白忙活了?
- We have to get to the surface. - What the hell?
我们必须马上回到水面上去!
We have to get to the surface now!
Lapidus 带我们上水面
Lapidus, take us up.
我们正在下潜呀!
We're divin'!
照办吧!
Just do it!
你听到他了吧 上去!
You heard him. Up!
- 哥们 那个玩意是怎么到潜艇上的? - Locke把它放我包里了
- Dude, how'd that get on the sub? - Locke put it in my pack.
他为什么要那样做? 他原本都想跟我们一起走的
Why would he do that? He wanted to come with us.
他确实想了 那就是我为什么要把他赶出去
You're damn right he did. That's why I shut his ass out.
他就是想让你把他赶出去 有人知道这个东西的工作原理吗?
He wanted you to shut him out. Any idea how that thing works?
- 我们可以把它关掉吗? - 这个表是与电池连接的
- Can we turn it off? - This watch is jury-rigged to the battery.
- 电池会引爆炸弹 - 还有多久才能浮上水面 Frank?
- The battery detonates the explosives. - How much time till we're up, Frank?
至少还有五分钟
At least five minutes.
我们没有那么多时间 接下来该怎么办 Sayid?
We ain't got five minutes. What's it gonna be, Sayid?
这些线... 是从表上引出来的
These wires... they're leads from the watch.
如果我们将线从电池上切断
If we disconnect them from the battery,
- 理论上讲 炸弹就会失效了 - "理论上"?
- technically speaking, the bomb should be inert. - "Technically"?
是的 但是你需要同时将它们全部拉出来
Yes, but you need to pull them out simultaneously,
- 我无法确定... - 靠边站
- and I'm not sure... - Step aside.
- 别 等下 等等 - 你这是要干什么了 医生?
- No, wait. Wait. - What the hell are you doing, doc?
啥事也不会发生的
Nothing's gonna happen.
- 什么? - 别把那些线拽出来
- What? - Don't pull those wires out.
没事的 一切都会好好的
We're okay. Nothing's gonna happen.
如果我不扯出这些线 Locke会把我们炸到
If I don't pull these wires, Locke's gonna blow us
- 天国去的 - 不 他不会的 Locke不会杀掉我们的
- to kingdom come. - No, he's not! Locke can't kill us.
呃... 什么?
Uh... What?
这就是他想要的 这就是他一直所期待的
This is what he wanted. This is what he's been waiting for.
他就是费尽心机把我们聚在这里
Everything that he has done has been to get us here.
他就是想要我们
He wanted to get us all in the same place
聚在一起... 在一个封闭的场所
at the same time... a nice enclosed space
- 一个我们都无法逃生的地方 - 我不明白
- where we had no hopes of getting out of. - I don't understand.
Locke说过 没有我们 他无法离开这个岛
Locke said that he can't leave the island without us.
我觉得 他的确无法离开这个岛
I think that he can't leave the island
除非我们都死了
unless we're all dead.
他告诉过我 他可以随时杀掉
He told me that he could kill any one of us
我们中的任何一个人 那么到现在他还没有动手
whenever he wanted, so what if he hasn't
是因为他... 他还不能这样做?
because he's... he's not allowed to?
如果他是想要我们自相残杀呢?
What if he's trying to get us to kill each other?
别挡着我 医生
Stay out of my way, doc.
现在 如果他想要那个炸弹爆炸
Now if he wanted that thing to blow up,
- 那为什么还放个计时器呢? 为什么不直接把它丢进来就好了? - 我不关心这些
- Why would he put a timer in it? Why not just throw it inside? - I don't care.
- 不会有事发生的 - 这事不是你说了算
- Nothing is gonna happen. - It's not your decision to make.
- 他杀不了我们! - 我是不会在这里坐以待毙的!
- He can't kill us! - I'm not gonna stand here and do nothing!
James啊...
James...
我们不会有事的
We are going to be okay.
你只需要相信我就好
You just have to trust me.
对不起 医生 我做不到
Sorry, doc, I don't.
仔细听着 在主岛上有口井
Listen carefully. There's a well on the main island
就在我们刚刚离开的营地 往南半英里的地方
a half mile south from the camp we just left.
Desmond被困在里面 Locke想杀掉他
Desmond's inside it. Locke wants him dead,
也就是说 你们有用得着他的地方 明白吗?
which mean you're going to need him. Do you understand me?
你告诉我这些干什么?
Why are you telling me this?
因为下一个就轮到你了 Jack
Because it's going to be you, Jack.
Sayid啊
Sayid!
喔 天呐
Oh, hell.
呃!
Uhh!
- 你还好吗? - 发生什么事了? Sayid刚才有没有...
- Are you okay? - What happened? Did Sayid just...
救命呀!
Help!
- Sun! - 救命呀!
- Sun! - Help!
等下!
Wait!
- 坚持下 我会把你救出来的 - Jin!
- Hold on. I'll get you out. - Jin!
不!
No!
- Sawyer! 我需要帮助! - Jin!
- Sawyer! I need help! - Jin!
Hurley啊
Hurley!
你带Kate离开这里
You gotta take Kate outta here.
- 那其他人怎么办? - 我会照顾他们的!
- What about everybody else? - I'll take care of them!
我必须找到Sayid!
I have to go after sayid!
再没有Sayid了!
There is no Sayid!
听我说 带着这个氧气瓶
Listen to me. Take this tank
你俩换着用 游到爆裂口那里去 行吗?
and buddy-breathe and swim out where the blast hole, okay?
Hurley 你能做到的 对吧?
Hurley, you can do this, okay?
好的
Okay.
走
Go.
医生!
Doc!
数三下
On three.
一... 二... 三
One... Two... Three.
Sawyer啊
Sawyer!
Jack啊
Jack!
Sawyer啊
Sawyer!
Sawyer.
Jin啊
Jin...
走呀
Go.
- 不 - 救你自己就好
- No. - Save yourself.
我一定会把你救出去的
I'm going to get you out of here.
走吧 走吧 我自己可以搞定的
Go. Go. I'll get her free.
不 我们一起来!
No. We can do this!
走吧! 救救Sawyer
Just go! Save sawyer.
Jin啊
Jin!
拿着这个 没有这个 我也能把他救出去
Take this. I can get him out without it.
不 你需要它的 Jack
No, you can't, Jack.
赶快走吧
Just go.
走
Go.
呃!
Uhh!
Jin啊
Jin.
再不走 就来不及了
You have to go.
不 我能救你的
No, I can do this.
不 不 你救不了
No. No, you can't.
走吧
Please go.
我是不会离开你的
I won't leave you.
我会救你出来的
I'm gonna get you out of here.
走呀
Go.
走啊 求你了
Go. Please.
走啊!
Go!
我不会抛下你不管的
我们再也不分开了
我爱你 Sun
I love you, Sun.
我爱你
I love you.
会有人来接你吧 Locke先生?
Is somebody meeting you, Mr. Locke?
对 我的未婚妻Helen会来
Yes,my fiancee Helen.
她 呃...
She's, uh...
可能遇上交通堵塞了
probably stuck in traffic.
嘿 你可以回去了
Hey, I'll take it from here.
你知道的 我对这个很拿手
You know, I'm pretty good at this.
- 嗯 祝你好运 先生 - 谢谢 再见
- Well, best of luck to you, sir. - Thank you. See ya.
Locke先生
Mr. Locke.
很高兴我没错过你出院
I'm glad I caught ya.
之前都没机会跟你说再见
I hadn't have a chance to say good-bye yet.
嗯 拜拜
Well, good-bye.
再次感谢你 Shephard医生
And thanks again, Dr. Shephard.
我去看你父亲了
I went to see your father.
什... 什么?
W... what?
当你拒绝做手术的时候
When you didn't want the surgery,
我感觉我应该去寻找问题根源
I felt like I had to understand why, and, uh, you know,
我想 如果我能弄清楚你因何会坐上轮椅
I thought that if I could find out why you're in this chair,
- 那也许就... - 我是因为坠机 才坐上轮椅的
- that maybe... - I was in a plane crash.
我拿到... 私人飞行员执照大概一周后
I had had my... my private pilot's license for a week,
嗯 我恳求我父亲当我第一个正式乘客
and, uh, I begged my father to be my first official passenger.
他有飞行恐惧症
He was terrified of flying.
但是我看着他的眼睛
But I looked him right in the eye
告诉他说 我能行的
and I told him he could trust me.
可我们只不过刚离开地面
And we barely got off the ground.
我... 我仍然记不起...
I... I still don't re...
我记不得我做错了什么
I don't remember what I did wrong,
但是那是我的错 都是我的错
but it was my fault. It was my fault
这个我深爱至极的男人
that this man who I loved more than anything
将再也无法行走... 或是说话...
will never walk or... talk or...
你知道的 我跟你第一次见面的时候
you know, the first time you and I met, um,
在机场... 的后面...
back at the... at the airport...
你告诉我 我的父亲已经永离尘世了
you told me that my father was gone,
说实话 呃
and, uh,
听到那我很伤心 但我知道你是对的
it hurt to hear that, but I knew you were right.
你的父亲也已经无力回天了 Locke先生
Your father's gone, too, Mr. Locke.
- 不 不 他不会的 - 嗯 他... 他的情况的确如此
- Uh, no, no, he's not. - Yes, he... he is,
无论你再怎么自责
and you can punish yourself as much as you want,
也不能让他回到从前
and that's never gonna bring him back.
事已至此了
What happened, happened,
那么...
and...
你别再纠结过往了
you can let it go.
别再纠结过往 你怎会以为如此简单?
What makes you think letting go is so easy?
不是的
It's not.
事实上 我也不知该怎么做 真的
In fact, I don't really know how to do it myself.
这就是我为什么希望...
And that's why I was hoping that...
也许你可以给我做个榜样
maybe you could go first.
再见了 Shephard医生
Good-bye, Dr. Shephard.
John 我能帮你的
I can help you, John.
我希望你相信我
I wish you believed me.
Jack啊
Jack.
我以为找不到你了
I couldn't find you.
- 他还好吧? - 他的头部受到强烈撞击
- Is he okay? - He got hit in the head pretty hard,
但是他还活着
but he's breathing.
Jin和Sun怎么样了?
What about Jin and Sun?
它沉下去了
It sunk.
什么 那个... 潜艇?
What, t... the submarine?
但是... 他们... 他们全都在上面
But... they... they were all on it.
所有人
Everyone.
- 他们... 他们都死了吗? - 不是所有的人
- What they're... they're all dead? - Not all of them.
等等 你... 你去哪?
Wait. W... where you going?
为我所做的事情 去画上句号
To finish what I started.